<Document>
  # Aurora's Song definitions and terms

  This section will explain some of the common terminology used on the server, both in character and out of character.

  ## IC (In Character) Terms

  ### ColComm
  Colonial Command is the main arm of the Auroran government present within the Aurora sector. In character this is often used to refer to the Admins (such as faxing ColComm about XYZ issue or incident).

  ### NFZ (No Fly Zone)
  A term occasionally used by the SLE to impose a restricted area in space, within a certain range, around a given area, wherein it is not permitted to go into without permission from the SLE, or another relevant authority.

  ### SLE
  Sector Law Enforcement, the policing force of the Aurora sector, whom upholds order and combats threats when necessary.

  ### SOP (Standard Operating Procedure)
  A term used to refer to the rules which certain employees of the Aurora sector (e.g SLE, Medics) [color=red]must[/color] follow at all times.

  ### Space Law
  The system of rules that characters should follow, which may be broken.

  ### SSD (Sudden Sleep Disease / Disorder)
  In character term for going AFK or disconnecting from the game. They are still considered to be alive and should be roleplayed as if they are asleep or otherwise unresponsive.

  ### UIV
  Unidentified Vessel, a ship with no designation that is part of either a criminal or more dangerous organization hostile to the Auroran government.

  ## OOC (Out of Character) Terms

  ### Ahelp
  Admin Help, which can be accessed via the F1 key to report issues or ask for help from the admin team.

  ### Levels of chat
  - IC (In Character): All conversations in world and in game, which take into consideration the lore and roleplay other players are having.
  - - Radio, which can be heard by everyone with the respective radio key.
  - - Local and Emote, which span the distance of your character (about seven tiles on each side).
  - - Whisper and Subtle, which span about a tile away from your character and are [color=red]not[/color] visible to ghosts. Bear in mind that whispers into Handicomms [color=red]are[/color] visible to ghosts.
  - OOC (Out of Character): All conversations which include knowledge present outside the game.
  - - OOC, used to communicate across the entire server (disabled mid-round).
  - - LOOC (Local OOC), which spans the distance of your character (about seven tiles on each side).
  - - Dead, which is similar to OOC, though only available to ghosts.

  ### Metacommunications
  The sharing of in game information through outside communications, such as Discord or another service, to gain an advantage in game.

  ### POI
  Point of Interest, used for every station that spawns at the start of the round and acts as a meeting point where shuttles can dock at (e.g Port Boreal, Little Byte Key, The Alley, and so on).

  ### Powergaming
  A display of a consistent pattern of antisocial and unsporting behavior in which a player prioritizes their game experience at the expense of others through routine optimization and abuse of game mechanics / knowledge.

  ### Safe zone
  Refers to areas including the Arrivals Relay, area, and its associated bus, which should not be modified, destroyed, or subject to antagonist activity.

  ### VGroid / VRoid
  Refers to the large, dangerous asteriods which spawn occasionally, their arrival being announced on the Supply channel.

</Document>

